<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <description>We quench your thirst for wisdom</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jul 2018 21:43:29 +0530</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Jul 2018 21:43:29 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.8.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Revelation about Steve Jobs</title>
        <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Here’s to the crazy ones, the misfits, the rebels, the troublemakers, the round pegs in the square holes… the ones who see things differently – they’re not fond of rules… You can quote them, disagree with them, glorify or vilify them, but the only thing you can’t do is ignore them because they change things… they push the human race forward, and while some may see them as the crazy ones, we see genius, because the ones who are crazy enough to think that they can change the world, are the ones who do.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;- Steve Jobs&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We all know who Steve Jobs is–he’s the genius who revolutionized modern technology and the mastermind who emphasized style as much as function in our everyday digital device. He built Apple into the world’s most valuable company and while he was at it, he transformed several other industries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;he-was-adopted&quot;&gt;He was adopted&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;His biological father, Abdulfattah Jandali, grew up in Syria and met his biological mother, Joanne Schieble at the University of Wisconsin. At the age of 23, they both thought it was too young to marry and having a child out of wedlock was unconventional so they gave their baby to Steve’s adoptive parents, Paul and Clara. They raised him on the promise that he would go to college.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;he-was-a-college-dropout&quot;&gt;He was a college dropout&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jobs graduated from Homestead High School in Silicon Valley, but dropped out of Reed College in Oregon because he didn’t want to spend his parent’s money. Although he did attend some classes, including calligraphy. In his 2005 commencement speech for Stanford University, Jobs stated that if he didn’t drop into that class the Mac wouldn’t have had multiple typefaces or proportionally spaced fonts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;he-experimented-with-psychedelics&quot;&gt;He experimented with psychedelics&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jobs experimented with LSD a few times claiming that it was a “profound experience” and “one of the most important things” in his life. He claimed it helped him to think differently.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;hewlett-packard-offered-jobs-a-summer-job&quot;&gt;Hewlett Packard offered Jobs a summer job&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When Jobs was 12 years old, HP co-founder Bill Hewlett offered him a summer job after Steve called him asking for parts for an electronics project. It was known that Jobs had a keen interest in engineering from a young age as he used to help his guardian, Paul, fix things on his workbench.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;he-was-fired-from-apple&quot;&gt;He was fired from Apple&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jobs was fired because Pepsi Executive John Sculley told the board that he was far too young. This was after Jobs recruited him. Jobs then started another project creating the NeXT computer, but sales were limited because it was too expensive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apple purchased NeXT stock resulting in Steve returning to Apple.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is a silver lining to this story - the combination of NeXT hardware with Apple resulted in operating systems like iOS used for the iPhone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/jobs-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;iwata&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;pixar-made-him-a-billionaire&quot;&gt;Pixar made him a Billionaire&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Have you ever wondered who Steve Jobs became a billionaire? Everyone assumes all of his money came from Apple, but his bank account actually made the biggest jump on a whole other project. Jobs was a majority shareholder of Pixar, previously know as the Graphics Group.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;he-was-a-tough-boss&quot;&gt;He was a tough boss&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He followed strict rules and principles.  He believed in being strict to follow that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;he-has-a-dedicated-team-to-study-emotions&quot;&gt;He has a dedicated team to study emotions&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jobs has a dedicated team to study the excitement and emotion behind opening a box and finding the products inside. This emotion is very common with Apple products today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/jobs-3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;iwata&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;he-patented-all-his-inventions&quot;&gt;He patented all his inventions&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Steve Jobs had close to 300 patents under his name. The glass staircase at the Apple store is one such patented attraction that pulls passers-by into the store.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;he-is-buried-in-an-unmarked-grave&quot;&gt;He is buried in an unmarked grave&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jobs was diagnosed with pancreatic cancer in 2003. He tried natural alternative healing such as becoming a vegan, acupuncture, and herbal remedies. He resisted medicine. Jobs died at his home in Palo Alto with his family at his side. His final words were “Oh wow. Oh wow. Oh wow.”&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/biography/2018/07/08/steve-jobs.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/biography/2018/07/08/steve-jobs.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>biography</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Everything you need to know about the nefarious Ted Bundy</title>
        <description>&lt;h3 id=&quot;who-was-ted-bundy&quot;&gt;Who was Ted Bundy?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Born in Burlington, Vermont, in 1946, Ted Bundy was one of the most notorious US serial killers of all time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Eleanor Louise Cowell gave birth to him at the Elizabeth Lund Home for Unwed Mothers and he was raised by his grandparents due to the stigma of being a “bastard”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He would later tell attorneys that his grandfather Samuel Cowell was a bully who would beat his wife, torture their dog and swing neighbourhood cats by their tails.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ted himself displayed deeply disturbing behaviour: His aunt Julia once awoke surrounded by knives and Bundy, three, standing by the bed smiling.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;when-did-he-start-killing-why-did-he-revisit-crime-scenes&quot;&gt;When did he start killing, why did he revisit crime scenes?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The date he started killing is up to debate though most agree it was 1974, around the time several women went missing in Seattle and Nearby Oregon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Locals started telling stories of how the women were being lured into cars by a young, dark-haired man named “Ted” who faked injuries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Soon after Bundy moved to Utah to attend law school in 1974, people started disappearing from there too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He was known to revisit some of his crime scenes to sexually violate the corpses of his victims.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How was Bundy arrested and how did he escape custody?
Bundy decapitated at least 12 of his victims and kept some of their heads as mementos of his vile acts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 1975, the maniac was arrested for kidnapping Carol DaRonch, one of the few who survived his attacks, and sentenced to up to 15 years behind bars.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Two years later, while acting as his own lawyer after being indicted over the death of a Colorado woman, Bundy jumped out of the jailhouse library window and disappeared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He was caught eight days later but in December the same year, 1977, he climbed out of a hole in the ceiling of his cell and fled to Florida.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In January 1978, he broke into the Chi Omega sorority at Florida State University and killed his four of among his final victims.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He was convicted of those crimes in July 1979 after bite marks on one of the bodies were found to be his.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;who-were-ted-bundys-victims&quot;&gt;Who were Ted Bundy’s victims?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bundy confessed to more than 30 murders across several states in the 70s but experts estimate the real number could exceed 100. Here are some of the victims we know about…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;how-was-ted-bundy-executed-and-how-did-people-celebrate&quot;&gt;How was Ted Bundy executed and how did people celebrate?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ted Bundy was executed on January 24, 1989, when he was 42-years-old.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There was a “circus atmosphere” outside the prison, according to journalist Jon Word who witnessed the final moments of dozens of death row killers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hundreds of people - including 20 off-duty police officers - sang, danced and set off fireworks in across the street from the prison as the execution was carried out.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/biography/2018/07/07/ted-bundy.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/biography/2018/07/07/ted-bundy.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>biography</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sigmund Freud</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Sigmund Freud was an Austrian neurologist and is one of the most renowned psychologist in the world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When the the Nazi Party took control of Germany they burned Sigmund Freud’s books he said, &lt;em&gt;“What progress we are making. In the Middle Ages they would have burned me. Now, they are content with burning my books.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He was a &lt;em&gt;‘glass is half full’&lt;/em&gt; kind of optimistic guy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They weren’t content with just that. He was actually on the Nazi’s “kill on sight” list for if they occupied the UK.
Little did they know by the time the Nazis got around to writing that list he was already dead…. but still. 
Another fun fact about Sigmund Freud is that when he had to sign a statement saying he was not mistreated by the Gestapo before he was allowed to leave, he supposedly facetiously wrote “I highly recommend the gestapo to everyone.” Anyway years later after his death they found that form and apparently he didn’t write that but just told everyone he did which is even funnier&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of Freud’s students, Wilhelm Reich , fled Europe during WWII and ended up in the US where the FDA burned all of his books because they didn’t agree with Reich’s thinking.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That only means we’re approaching the era where we burn the people who read the books.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/interesting/2018/07/07/sigmund-freud.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/interesting/2018/07/07/sigmund-freud.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>interesting</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>This CEO cut his own pay instead of blaming the workers</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;When Nintendo had a fall in revenue in 2014, from the less successful Wii U its CEO, Satoru Iwata cut his own pay in half for 5 months rather than blaming the workers. Other members of the board also took a pay cut of between 20 and 30 per cent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Analysts have criticised the system’s limited game selection, as rivals Sony and Microsoft enjoy robust demand for their new PlayStation 4 and Xbox One consoles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Nintendo’s worse-than-expected performance is mainly due to a slump in the Wii U,” said Hideki Yasuda, a games analyst at Ace Securities in Tokyo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“They haven’t released attractive games titles which slammed the brakes on console sales. Also, its rivals have seen strong demand for their consoles which is taking market share away from Nintendo.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even though this was a bold move. In retrospect, this is a classic Japanese CEO move. Many heads of Japanese corporations slash pays from the top instead of from the bottom. Sony of Japan did the same as well. This is how companies should handle losses, more often than not they cut the jobs of people who put so much work into the company. All while not taking a single dollar from the highest earning individuals. Nintendo is lucky enough to have always had very honorable high-ranking employees who not only care about the well being of the brand but also their community’s growth and responses. This is just another instance of the now deceased Iwata-san proving just how selfless and compassionate he was.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/iwata-rip.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;iwata&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is Satoru Iwata we’re talking about, the most passionate, selfless CEO that existed. His famous quote was :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“On my business card, I am a corporate president. In my mind, I am a game developer. In my heart, I am a gamer”.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This man lived for Nintendo, he helped the team working on the original Pokemon games by programming the version that would go out to America. He had passion for the game and respect for his workers. The very sad part is that he passed away with the regret of having disappointed Nintendo fans following a poor E3 in 2015. He’s a huge inspiration and was deeply loved by all of Nintendo both employees and fans. Unfortunately, he died in July, 2014 due to complications from a tumor in his bile duct.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/interesting/2018/07/07/satoru-iwata.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/interesting/2018/07/07/satoru-iwata.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>interesting</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Minimalism: Less is more</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;This intriguing film asks a question we should all be asking ourselves:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“How might your life be better with less?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When Joshua Fields Millburn packs for a trip, he uses a single duffle bag. It contains two button-up shirts, a few T-shirts, a stack of underwear, jacket, toiletries bag, laptop, and a blow dryer. He’s already wearing his single pair of jeans and shoes, so those don’t need to be packed. And that’s it – he’s off and away for a ten-month book tour around the country.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Millburn, together with his childhood friend Ryan Nicodemus, is one of The Minimalists. The two-man team is on a mission to spread a message that less is more, that letting go of material possessions opens people up to better human relationships and more meaningful lives, not to mention free time and saved money. They have found a receptive audience. Millions of readers flock to their website, updated regularly with thoughtful blog posts and podcasts, seeking advice on how to focus on the things that really matter in life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, Millburn and Nicodemus have been featured in a new film called “Minimalism: A Documentary About the Important Things.” Released in 2016, it has been called “the #1 indie documentary of the year,” thanks to impressive box-office numbers. The 78-minute film follows Millburn and Nicodemus on their book tour across the United States, reading, speaking, and hugging people along the way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Crowds grow steadily in size, from a handful of people at an event at SXSW music festival in August 2014 to standing room only at The Last Bookstore in Los Angeles ten months later.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While Millburn and Nicodemus are the film’s main story arc, “Minimalism” features many other fascinating people, all of whom are seeking meaning in life through simplicity. These include scientists, who examine the psychological reasons for our human obsession with constantly acquiring more and why we’re never happy; an architect who argues that we should be designing homes to fit our lives, not the other way around; a journalist who copes with stress through meditation; a world traveler who carries everything on his back; authors who write about clutter-free living, minimalist parenting, and the importance of turning off our phones; and even TreeHugger’s founder Graham Hill, who now runs Life Edited.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was pleased to see Courtney Carver’s Project 333 featured on the film, too, as I’ve written about her popular ‘capsule wardrobe’ approach in the past.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The film is inspiring. It was emotional to learn about the tragic childhoods that both Nicodemus and Millburn experienced, with their drug addict and alcoholic mothers. It makes one realize that, despite earlier financial successes, they do not come from a position of white privilege, but one of real poverty and challenge. It makes their message all the more poignant.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you watch the film, you may have the same reaction as I did – reach for my phone and turn it off as the credits rolled. Instead of wasting time and mental energy scrolling through social media before bed, I felt inspired to disconnect completely. That was 12 hours ago and my phone is still off. It feels amazing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Minimalism” is currently available on Netflix, Amazon, iTunes, Google Play, Vimeo, and can be purchased on DVD.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/review/2018/07/07/minimalism.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/review/2018/07/07/minimalism.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>review</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Michael Jordan was mocked for being stingy</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Michael Jordan once tipped a waitress a $5 chip for bringing him a drink. Wayne Gretzky stopped the waitress, removed the $5 chip, grabbed one of the many $100 chips on Jordan’s side of the table, and gave it to her. Then he said, “That’s how we tip in Las Vegas, Michael.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People who work in the casino industry have hilarious stories about celebrities and their out-on-the-town exploits, usually they involve some famous celebrity doing something dumb in a drunken stupor. These stories can be funny or interesting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rich Strafella, a VP and long-time gaming exec at the Hard Rock Hotel in Las Vegas, was recently asked to share his favorite celebrity story.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“I remember a night when Wayne Gretzky insulted Michael Jordan at the table. It was a private salon game. Michael had ordered a drink from the cocktail waitress, and he gave her a five-dollar chip. Wayne took it off the cocktail waitress’s tray, gave it back to Michael, grabbed a hundred-dollar chip from Michael’s stack and put it on the cocktail waitress’s tray. Then he said, “That’s how we tip in Las Vegas, Michael.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Charles Barkley told a story about Michael Jordan in front of him. Charles was going to give a homeless man 5 dollars and Jordan stopped him. Jordan said in front of them, &lt;em&gt;“if he can take the time to say,” can you spare a dollar”,&lt;/em&gt; he can spend the time to say, &lt;em&gt;“welcome to McDonald’s, can I take your order”.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jordan’s teammate Scottie Pippen was also notoriously cheap and earned the nickname “No Tippin’ Pippen” among restaurant workers. One of the blackjack delaers claim to have experienced the same: &lt;em&gt;“I dealt blackjack to MJ and a few other Bulls players at a Connecticut casino back in the day. Can confirm he is a jerk to deal to anyway. No tips from him or his crew for the few hours I dealt to them in the high limit area and an all around rude attitude.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“You pocket 100% of the tips you don’t give.” - Michael Jordan&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/interesting/2018/07/07/michael-jordan.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/interesting/2018/07/07/michael-jordan.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>interesting</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Are We Living in a Computer Simulation?</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;High-profile physicists and philosophers often gather to debate whether we are real or virtual—and what it means either way&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you, me and every person and thing in the cosmos were actually characters in some giant computer game, we would not necessarily know it. The idea that the universe is a simulation sounds more like the plot of “The Matrix,” but it is also a legitimate scientific hypothesis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During an interview, Elon Musk said, “There’s a one in billions chance we’re in base reality.” This essentially means that he believes that more likely than not (by a lot), the world that we know is just a very sophisticated computer simulation. Neil deGrasse Tyson put the odds at 50-50 that our entire existence is a program on someone else’s hard drive. “I think the likelihood may be very high,” he said. He noted the gap between human and chimpanzee intelligence, despite the fact that we share more than 98 percent of our DNA. Somewhere out there could be a being whose intelligence is that much greater than our own. “We would be drooling, blithering idiots in their presence,” he said. “If that’s the case, it is easy for me to imagine that everything in our lives is just a creation of some other entity for their entertainment.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If it turns out we really are living in a version of “The Matrix,” though—so what? “Maybe we’re in a simulation, maybe we’re not, but if we are, hey, it’s not so bad,” said David Chalmers, a professor of philosophy at New York University.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“My advice is to go out and do really interesting things, so the simulators don’t shut you down.” said Tegmarks, a cosmologist from MIT.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But some were more contemplative, saying the possibility raises some weighty spiritual questions. “If the simulation hypothesis is valid then we open the door to eternal life and resurrection and things that formally have been discussed in the realm of religion,” said James Gates, a theoretical physicist at the University of Maryland. “The reason is quite simple: If we’re programs in the computer, then as long as I have a computer that’s not damaged, I can always re-run the program.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And if someone somewhere created our simulation, would that make this entity God? “We in this universe can create simulated worlds and there’s nothing remotely spooky about that,” Chalmers said. “Our creator isn’t especially spooky, it’s just some teenage hacker in the next universe up.” Turn the tables, and we are essentially gods over our own computer creations. “We don’t think of ourselves as deities when we program Mario, even though we have power over how high Mario jumps,” Tyson said. “There’s no reason to think they’re all-powerful just because they control everything we do.” And a simulated universe introduces another disturbing possibility. “What happens,” Tyson said, “if there’s a bug that crashes the entire program?”&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/science/2018/07/07/comp-sim.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/science/2018/07/07/comp-sim.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>Science</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why Billy Joel never sells front row seats in his concerts?</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;In an interview with Billboard, Bill Joel said:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“We never sell front rows, we hold those tickets at just about every concert. For years, the scalpers got the tickets and would scalp the front row for ridiculous amounts of money. Our tickets are cheap, under $100, some in the $80s, the highest is about $150.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’d look down and see rich people sitting there, I call ‘em “gold chainers.” Sitting there puffing on a cigar, “entertain me, piano man.” They don’t stand up, make noise, sit there with their bouffant haired girlfriend lookin’ like a big shot. I kinda got sick of that, who the hell are these people, where are the real fans? It turns out the real fans were always in the back of the room in the worst seats. We now hold those tickets, and I send my road crew out to the back of the room when the audience comes in and they get people from the worst seats and bring ‘em in to the front rows.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This way you’ve got people in the front row that are really happy to be there, real fans. We’ve tried to figure out how to beat the scalpers for years and years, hold off selling until the last minute, the wristband thing, limiting the amount of tickets people can get. You can’t fight that secondary market. There used to be anti-scalping laws and they let them lapse from the books. My theory is there’s a lot of tax revenue in those secondary ticket markets, these guys selling tickets for $500 to $1,000 gotta pay tax on it, and a lot more goes to government than there would be based on my ticket prices. So why should they enforce the scalping laws.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We don’t want to play to big shots, I want to play to younger people, people who can only afford a low ticket price. They make the best audience, they make the most noise, they’re the most enthusiastic. It’s just hard to get to them any more. I tell the audience every night, “I hope you didn’t pay more than face value on that ticket, because we ain’t worth more than that, and you ain’t gonna get any more than that.”&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/interesting/2018/07/07/billy-joel.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/interesting/2018/07/07/billy-joel.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>interesting</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
